这天真热
Can't get over this heat.
天呐 你们办公室就是个地狱
Swear to God, they put your office on top of hell.
我知道你要走了
I know you have to get going.
是的 Doyle参议员有点固执
I do. Senator Doyle's kind of a stikler.
对 对 他看起来就是个老顽固
Yeah. Yeah, he seems like a massive stickler.
就像我刚才说的 我们参议员 很有时间做冗长辩论改革
Well, like I was saying, the senator has a lot of time for filibuster reform.
这是底线 Eric 我们需要他支持这个法案
Bottom line here, Eric, we need him to sponsor this bill.
不好意思
Excuse me.
天呐 这个胃肠性感冒
God, this gastric bug,
搞得我头晕晕的
it's got my head all jammed up
拉肚子就像打雷
and my ass is like the thunderdome.
好啊 让暴风雨来得更猛烈吧
Yeah! Boom, come to mama!
对不起 不是对你说 这个 离开下
Sorry, not you. This. Excuse me.
噢 天呐 无法承受之热啊
Oh, my God, this heat is just unbearable.
我觉得自己变壁虎了
I feel like a gecko.
不好意思打扰下 不过 他奶奶孙女的大爷
Sorry to interrupt, but fuck-a-deedoo-dah, fuck-a-Dee-ay!
Martin在白宫  怎样
Martin At The White House. - What?
绿色产业工作小组有希望得绿灯 感叹号
Clean jobs task force likely to be green lit! Exclamation point.
耶 我的天
Yeah! Oh, my God!
果断对我有利啊
That is so great for me.
还有国家  对 对 对 我就是这个意思
- And the country. - Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what I meant.
噢 Amy 干得好 Amy
Oh, Amy. Good job, Amy.
干得好  不然我怎么能拿到钱
- Good job. - That's why I get paid the medium bucks.
受益无穷  必须的
- This is legacy stuff. - Yeah, it is.
姐要追究污染企业的责任
Polluting corporations held accountable by me.
终结对国外石油的依赖
Dependence on foreign oil ended by me.
能别吹了吗  就快了
Could you stop that? - really close.
我让Sue给白宫的Mart打电话
I'm gonna get Sue to call Mart at the White House.
我得送走Doyle参议员的幕僚长
I still need to say goodbye to senator Doyle's chief of staff.
噢 他还在吗
Oh, is he still here?
知道我要做什么吧 擦身而过
You know what I'm gonna do? Brush past.
给他笑一个 带回去给老板交差
Give him a smile to take back to his boss.
行  你会走哪条路
Okay. - Which way are you going?
走电梯 第一个门  好
- Elevator bank, first door. - Okay. Yeah.
Eric 不好意思
Eric, apologies.
哦 Sue 总统打了电话没
Oh, Sue, did the President call?
没有  没? 好吧
No. - No? Okay.
一切都还好吧  哦 对 都挺好的
- Everything okay? - Oh, yeah, things are great.
那好啊  是很好
Good. - Things are Great.
那么 行呗 副总统下午会过去
So, yeah, the Vice President will see you this afternoon.
见你和参议员
We'll see the senator and yourself.
呃 这个文件很不错
Um, this is an interesting piece of paper.
哦 副总统女士 记得Eric吧
Oh, madam Vice President, you remember Eric.
噢 必须的 Eric  副总统女士
- Oh, of course. Eric. - Madam Vice President.
你好吗  病菌闹了点小毛病
- How are you? - I've got a little bit of the bug,
除了那个外还是不错的
but other than that, I'm good.
很抱歉听到那个 多喝液体
I'm sorry to hear that. Well, drink plenty of liquid.
这么说还挺笨的 是不是
Well, that's sort of a stupid thing to say, isn't it?
你又不能喝固体 对吧
'Cause you can't drink a solid, can you?
汤?
Soup?
话说 汤是由固体悬浮在液体而组成 算起来还是液体
Well, soup is solids suspended in liquid, so it qualifies as a liquid.
看到没 Gary在弗吉尼亚大学主修科学
See that? Gary was a major at U.V.A. in science.
偶尔是有用的
So occasionally that's of use.
那我们下午见了
So we'll see you guys this afternoon.
很好 很高兴见到您  很高兴见到你
Great. Nice to See you. - So Nice to See you.
多保重 汤?
Take care. Soup?
要Selina批的新闻稿
Press release for Selina approval.
嘿 Mike 你的汗...  我知道
- Hey, Mike, your perspiration... - I know.
我就是说说  管不了 健康的身体要流汗
- I'm just saying. - Can't help it. Sign of a healthy body.
还是有这方面产品的 Mike  我都试过了
- There are products available, Mike. - I tried them all.
全被我的汗水穿透了 大毛孔的悲哀
Sweat right through 'em. I got very large pores.
嘿 伙计们 开个短会 可以吧
Hey, guys, quick sidebar meeting, okay?
来了 来了  Lowden参议员的人来不了了
- Yeah, yeah. - Senator Lowden's guy canceled.
他也是胃肠性感冒
He has the gastric flu, too.
他非死不可状态写着 上帝能不能对人家的内裤仁慈点
His Facebook status is may God have mercy on my boxers.
对 我看到了 写得好
Yeah, I saw that. I liked it.
嘿 Dan 开个窗 好吗
Hey, Dan, can you get some more oxygen in here, please?
好
Yeah.
这个完全没用啊 话说
This thing is completely useless, by the way.
放个屁都能更助于空气流动
Can move more air by farting.
你可以的 女士
I'm sure you can, ma'am.
这些不能开 是反自杀窗
Those don't open. Those are anti-suicide windows.
因为你来上班了他们才装的这个吧 Gary
They only put those in after you started working here, right, Gary?
是这样的
So, here's the deal.
绿色产业稳操胜券 这很好
Clean jobs in the bag. So that's good.
但是我们还要应付下午的 冗长辩论改革
But we've got filibuster reform talks this afternoon that we've got to deal with.
专注这一个 好吧 伙计们
So let's nail this, okay, everybody?
攻占这个议程  听起来像你要搞政变
- Let's seize the agenda. - You're making it sound like a coup.
总统去南非了姐很开心 这点不否认
I'm not gonna say I'm not enjoying the President being in South Africa.
天 在狮子保护区戴着那什么围巾
God, wearing some kind of shawl at a lion sanctuary.
看到那照片没 简直不敢相信
Did you see that photo? It's unbelievable.
总之 我刚说到重新定义...
Anyway, I'm just talking about redefining...
Dan 你开会经常用的那句怎么说来着
Dan, what was that phrase that you used in our meeting?
是什么  两点论
- What was that? - Two point me.
两点论 就是这个 姐爱死了
Two point me. That's exactly right. I love that.
女士 你跟Glen Yates的两小时日程取消了
Ma'am, your two-hour with Glen Yates just canceled.
他也胃肠性感冒了
He's got the bug.
行呗 这代表我有两小时空闲了
All right, well, that means I've got two hours free.
走起来 伙计们
Let's capitalize on this, you guys.
来 我们去走走 见见公众
C'mon, let's go somewhere. Let's meet the public.
你要把它标准化么  是的 没错
- You want to normalize it? - Yes, exactly.
我需要的是固定的标准 到哪里找
I want to meet some regular normals. Where we gonna find them?
影像操作吧 各种正规
Photo op with the normals and the normalistas.
有个书展...  噢 天呐
- There's a book fair... - Oh, my God.
在Adams Morgan  太沉闷了 不行
- ...in Adams Morgan. - Too dull, no.
抱着书能照出什么好照片
You're not gonna get a good photo holding a book.
要活泼点  跟小朋友一起读书什么的啊
- You need something active. - It's like kids read or something.
小朋友才是最难掌握的 他们会尿裤子
Kids are unpredictable. They wet their pants.
简单点 简单点  对 不好
- Keep it simple. Keep it simple. - Yeah, not good.
女士 冷冻酸乳酪 知道吧 本市大热啊
Ma'am, frozen yoghurt, all right, is huge in this town right now.
外面这么热 我们去商店
It's hot out. Let's go to a store.
我知道U街有家 我经常去
There's one that I know that I go to all the time on U Street.
非裔美国人开的 三代了
It's owned by three generations of African-Americans.
各种故事啊 有没有
I mean there's a narrative built right in.
很棒 完美 就这么定了
Excellent. Perfect. Done deal.
他们就是标准
We can totally normalize with those guys.
就做这个 动起来 伙计们
That's what we're gonna do. Make it happen, guys.
好 我们去酸乳酪屋
All right, we're going to a yoghurt shop.
你跟Selina两点论的那个会是什么时候
When was this two point me meeting with Selina?
你还在查我的每个行动吗
Oh, are you still tracking my every move?
我以为咱俩已经达成共识往前看了呢
I thought we agreed to move on.
从哪儿往前看 我们不过谈了一星期恋爱
Move on from what? We dated for like a week.
感觉就像慢性食物中毒
It was like getting of a mild food poisoning.
这样 Amy 真心抱歉 我的到来
Look, Amy, I am genuinely sorry that my arrival here
不仅让你变得难为情 还小涨了体重
has caused you to become so self-conscious and gain a little weight.
去死吧
Fuck point you.
我们是不是早了  是
are We early? - Yeah.
我就想早点到
I want to get there early.
我想要准时到的人产生迟到的错觉
I want the people who are on time to think that they're late.
哦 思维游戏 爱死了  是吧
- Oh, mind games. Love it. - Yeah.
我不喜欢之前
I didn't appreciate the reference
自杀倾向的那个影射 我不是个笑话
to my potential suicide earlier. I'm not a joke.
对 你是唇膏帝 Gary
No, you're the guy with the big bag of lip balm, Gary.
你就是他妈的基辛格
You're fucking kissinger.
你对我说的每一句都不友善
Every single thing you say to me is emasculating.
意识到没  当然
do you realize that? - Yes.
我觉得Doyle参议员对于法案促进 不会太积极
I think that senator Doyle still might go cold on sponsoring this bill.
那我们要帮他积极起来 我们要他帮忙支持
Well, 've got to warm him up, 'cause we need his support on
那个抛弃多余还是叫什么的
junk the jams or whatever they're calling it now.
去除冗余  去除冗余?
Unclog The backlog. - Unclog The backlog?
我的工作很严肃的
I do a serious job.
我是离副总统最近的人
I'm next to the veep more than any other human being.
你在更远的轨道
You are distantly orbiting her.
我才是她的月亮
I'm her moon.
那你会为她挡子弹吗 Gary
So would you take a bullet for the veep, Gary?
哦 上帝  不 不
- Oh, my God. - No, no, no.
你要知道 你刚好站在射击范围内
Because, you know, you're gonna be right in the line of fire.
那不是我的工作 如果她倒下了 我会帮她
It's not my job. I would help her if she was down.
对 如果她的嘴被枪击了 你会上唇膏
Right, with the lip balm if she got shot in the lips.
那可以重创敌人
That could crack 'em pretty bad.
太好了 我们没上电梯
Great, we missed the elevators.
Doyle很重要 他就像参议院的俄罗斯套娃
Doyle is essential. He's like the Russian doll of the Senate.
里面还有小参议员
Comes with little senators inside of him.
嘿 Gary 可以给我张纸巾吗
Hey, Gary, can I have a kleenex?
人呢  哦 来了
- Where are my people? - Oh, here they go.
快点
Come on.
不要生气 不要生气 拜托
Don't shoot. Don't shoot. Please don't shoot.
生气吧 骂他
Shoot him. You can shoot him.
你们到底去哪儿了
Where the hell did you go?
Dan 你得上车  哦 当然
- Dan, you're gonna have to go in the limo. - Oh, sure, yeah.
女士 我觉得现在可以
Ma'am, I think we should start ramping up the whole launch
实施两点论了
of two point you right now.
放点暗示出来
You know, just kind of a little hint out there
说说绿色产业会怎样
about what clean jobs is gonna be.
对 我也这么想  我可以搞定
- Yeah, I think the same thing. - I can get right on this.
Leon West给了我他的私人号码
Leon West has given me his private cell.
噢 太好了 Doyle会议后
Oh, good. All right, let's set up 10 minutes
安排十分钟跟他见面
of face time with him after the Doyle meeting.
收到 马上办
Copy that, I'm on it.
知道吗 对于Doyle我有点紧张
You know what? I'm nervous about Doyle.
他是个怪人  他是个老顽固
- He can be a real hogfucker. - He's a stickler.
等等 洗手液 女士
Wait a minute. Hand sanitizer, ma'am.
知道我听到什么吗 Doyle参议员穿连裤袜
You know what I heard? Senator Doyle wears pantyhouse.
真的假的
Oh, really?
假的 但是你想到这个 就没那么怕了
No. But now that you have that image, he's not that scary.
听着 告诉Dan
Oh, listen, tell Dan
酸乳酪屋计划开始 好吧
to start working on the yoghurt store, okay?
等等 Gary
Wait a minute, Gary.
Gary 这也太多了
Gary, this is way too much.
你要我做什么 干嘛
What do you want me to do? What?
好了 不准有下次 听到没
Okay, let's not do that again, all right?
Andrew 你好吗 -
Andrew, how are you?
副总统女士 很荣幸见到你
Madam Vice President, a pleasure.
别这样 请叫我Selina
Oh, come on. Selina, please.
还是要按规矩来
Well, let's play this one by the book.
Eric 在这儿  我们早上见过
- Eric, of course. - We just saw him this morning.
对 你们谈到汤
Yeah, you spoke about soup.
那么... 我们开始吗
So... should we get to it?
开始吧  那就...好
- Let's get to it. - Let's... okay.
我要把文件放下  请随意
- I'm gonna lighten this up a little bit. - Please. Please do.
大家好
Hi, everybody.
今天有很多要说的
Well, we have lots to talk about.
对 说起来
Yup, let's do some talking.
你要我支持这个方案  对的
- You need me to sponsor this bill. - Yes, I do.
我想你帮我 也想知道你想我帮你什么
I do need you to do that. And I want to know what you need from me.
你要什么 非拨出专项拨款
What do you need? You need some non-earmark earmarks?
还是需要连任的支持
You need support during your reelection campaign?
我不会被拍到吃热狗
I just won't be photographed eating a hot dog
或者其他长得像生殖器的食物了
or any other phallic food.
真糟 那是个错误
Oops. That was mistake.
我不需要那些 女士  好
- Really don't need any of that, ma'am. - Okay.
我要的很简单
What I need is very simple.
实际上就是...
Actually, what I would like...
干什么 Eric
What the hell, Eric?
怎么了 刚发生了什么
What was that? What just happened?
他要对你打喷嚏 我挡住了
He was gonna seze on you and I blocked it.
真对不起 副总统女士
I am so sorry, madam Vice President.
干得好 Eric 我是说 你要再来一次吗
That is nice work, Eric. I mean, you want to take another shot?
我们在这边 还没被喷到
I don'think we're drenched at this end of the table.
天呐 对不起  吓死我了
- Oh, my God. I'm sorry. - That scared me to death.
他就是娘的一个镀金轰炸机
He can be a gold-plated fucking shit gibbing.
他是你下属  他差点对你的脸打了喷嚏
- He works for you. - I mean, he almost sneezed in your face.
赤裸裸的背叛 给你上杯咖啡吧
I think it's treason. Let me get you a cup of coffee.
咖啡好啊
I would love a cup of coffee.
噢 我的天
Oh, my goodness.
听着 我可以搞定这里
Listen, I've got this covered now.
好吧 你去多叫些参议员过来
Okay? Why don't you go round up a few more senators?
好 你确定  确定 干掉冗长辩论
- Okay, you sure? - Mm-hmm, filibuster smackdown.
我就是这个意思  好 干起来
- That's what I call it. - All right, dig it.
哇 我还在抖 你们呢
Oh, wow, I'm shaking from that. Are you guys?
不 我们绝对清楚Murray参议员的立场
No, we perfectly understand senator Murray's reservations.
当然 她总是跟着自己的良心走
Yeah, of course, she must be guided by her conscience.
不会不开心
No hard feelings whatsoever.
呃 Dan?  怎么
- Uh, Dan? - Yeah?
我希望你不会误解我的意思
I hope you don't take this the wrong way,
不过我能不能说 你就是个混蛋
but can I just say? You kinda look like an asshole.
你告诉他们了吗 Amy 哦 不是吧
Hello. Did you tell them, Amy? Oh, come on. Come on.
我为副总统挡了子弹  你怎么会挡子弹 Gary
- I took a bullet for the veep. - How'd you take a bullet, Gary?
是个喷嚏弹 直射面部
It was a sneeze bullet. Right in the face.
救Selina于水火 纯本能
Saved Selina from the bug. Pure instinct.
就是个脏弹... 嘣...
It was like a dirty bomb and I... bam...
我冲出去了 嗯
Dived on it. Mmm!
嘿 马屁精们好
Hey, hey, it's the flunkies.
都说你们工作没做好
And people say you're bad at your jobs.
你是来当间谍的么 Jonah  我不是
- You here to spy, Jonah? - I'm not here to spy.
我在白宫上班 我可以只是路过来说
I work at the White House, so I can just walk in and say,
我是白宫来的 你们他妈在干嘛
I'm from the White House. What the fuck are you doing?
什么 你在白宫上班
What? You work at the White House?
天呐 我可以打你吗  呃 你可以
- Oh, my God. Can I blow you? - Uh, yes, you can.
待会走廊见
I will meet you out in the hallway in a few seconds.
好 我会拿个活梯来
Sure, I'll get a stepladder.
总之 我是白宫来的 你们他妈在干嘛
Anyway, I work for the White House. What the fuck are you doing?
在想应该给副总统什么口味的冻酸乳酪
Trying to figure out what flavor frozen yoghurt the veep should get.
薄荷
Mint.
代表着新鲜 信任 传统价值观
It implies freshness, trust, traditional values.
不错啊  这是我的领域
Fascinating. - this is one of my areas.
选食物 说真的 写一下
Yeah, food choices. Seriously, put it up.
哦 漩涡 种族和谐 跨越鸿沟
Oh, swirl. Racial harmony and crossing the aisle.
那就是饼干和奶油
So is cookies and cream.
白宫 我是Jonah
White House. This is Jonah.
小心头
Okay. Watch your head.
噢 去你妈的 不 不是说你 先生
Oh, fuck you. No, not you, sir.
对于冗长辩论改革法案 我很兴奋
Very excited about this filibuster reform bill.
听到这个真高兴
That is great to hear.
如果你能拿到参议院改良法案
If you can get a Senate reform bill
就代表它的确需要改
through the place it's designed to reform,
这是惊人的  对
that would be amazing. - Yeah.
我是指 这就像
I mean, that would be like
劝服一个人打自己一拳
persuading a guy to fist himself.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
告诉我 Flatterbox先生
Tell me, Mr. Flatterbox,
你需要我做什么 说真的
what do you need from me, really?
我需要你让那些石油产业
Well, I need you to keep oil guys
离绿色产业小组远点
off the clean jobs task force.
不要这样 Andrew  我就是要这样 对
- Don't do this to me, Andrew. - I'm going to do it to you, yup.
这是个微妙的区域
This is a nuanced area.
你跟石油产业不是一边的吗
You are not in the pocket of oil?
不是 我们不是一边的
No, I'm not in the pocket of oil. No.
我们可以做到的
So we can make this work.
我很想做点实事  对
- I'm eager to be constructive. - Right.
看起来好像我做得到 那么我...
It seems to me that somehow we can make this happen, then I'd...
成交 你让石油产业远离绿色产业
Deal. You keep oil guys off clean jobs,
我就会支持法案
I will sponsor the filibuster bill.
我们可以做…
Well, we can work...
得到
This out.
太好了  真好
Great. Terrific. - Wonderful.
咖啡  哈?
coffee. - Hmm?
杯子?  哦 是的
- Cup? - Oh, uh-huh. Sure.
Gary Doyle参议员的幕僚就像要死了一样
Gary, senator Doyle's guy looks like he's dying.
如果我是你 我就会上药房 把所有药都买一份
If I were you, I would go straight to the pharmacy and take one of everything.
在去药房的路上我就爆发了
I'm gonna have a blowout if I walk to the pharmacy.
这是我担心的
That's what I'm worried about.
如果你要拉在裤子上 就不要坐在这
If you're gonna shit your pants, I don't want you here.
嘿  我觉得自己做对了
- Hey. - I think I did the right thing,
但还是要你确认一下
but I just need you to confirm that I did the right thing.
我对某人说了某事
I said something to someone.
你具体说了什么 女士 对谁说的
What exactly did you say, ma'am, and to who?
对谁
To whom.
Doyle参议员说他会支持法案...
Senator Doyle said that he would sponsor the bill...
Oh!
如果我们让石油产业远离绿色产业的话
If we keep oil off of clean jobs.
这里有个暗示 也许...
And there was an implication, perhaps...
你没说好吧  没
- You didn't say yes? - No.
我没说 好
I didn't say yes.
我说的是 嗯
I said yeah.
是这样 我们对石油产业说可以让他们插一脚
Okay, well, we told oil we'd put one of their guys on clean jobs.
所以我们才能在那条餐具围脖上全身而退
That's why we got away with the cutlery tweet.
我知道 知道
I know, I know.
她知道  我只是被Doyle迷住了
- She's aware of that. - Okay, I was charmed by Doyle.
他眼睛在闪烁
He's got that little twinkle in his eye.
他说到给人家一拳
He was talking about fisting people.
他对我很好 我很开心
He just niced me. I got niced.
你当时在哪 Amy
And where were you, Amy, by the way?
不 你说你能搞定
No, you said you had it covered.
没有 我搞不定 而且你的工作就是
No, I didn't have it covered. And it's your job to know
在我说能搞定的时候看出来我搞不定 并且帮我搞定
that if I say I have it covered, I don't have it covered and you cover me.
我需要你们帮我收回那些话
I need you all to make me have not said that.
我要你们...帮我撤回那些话
I need you to have... make me unsaid it.
我们先慢慢理一下
Let's just slow down for a second.
做两栏 一个冗长辩论 一个绿色产业
Make two columns, one with filibuster, one with clean jobs,
因为它们现在是相对的
because now they are versus.
Doyle在冗长辩论上帮我们 把他放那儿
Doyle gives us filibuster, so put him there.
好 但是石油业能帮绿色产业
Okay, but oil gives us clean jobs.
绿色产业是你的主力  是的
clean jobs is your legacy. - Yes.
等等  干嘛
- Hold on a second. - What?
我们能不能把一个曾经是石油业的人 放进绿色小组
What if we put an ex-oil guy on the task force?
懂我意思吗
You see what I'm saying?
一个以前做石油的 不是很石油的
Someone who's cozy with oil, but not active oil.
前石油业  那是撒谎
- Former oil. - That's lying.
创意语义学
Creative semantics.
创意的语义来表达我们在撒谎
Well, that's a creatively semantic way of saying we're lying.
那也是创意
Still creative.
哦 嘿Jonah Jonah Jonah
Oh, hey, Jonah. Jonah. Jonah.
我们... 我们在...
That we... yeah, that we might like.
我要说的是 我们先跟随我刚说的
What I'm saying is that we go with what I just said,
那个 呃 那个...
the, um, the...
牙买加朗姆酒口味
Jamaican rum flavor.
这个选择真心重口味
That's a really strong flavor choice.
我是说 很意外
I mean, it's unexpected,
很古怪 有点性意义
it's funky, it's kind of sexual.
对 我也不想太快做决定
Yeah, I don't want to make too quick of a decision.
考虑下其他口味吧
Let's consider other flavors.
比如香草味  拜托 女孩子才吃香草
- Like vanilla. - Oh, c'mon. Vanilla is a girl's flavor.
不 我没选择 Amy
No, I have no choice here, Amy.
因为我被逼到墙角了
Because I was backed into a corner.
所以其他口味对我来说都不算选择 知道吧
So other flavors aren't an option for me, okay?
也许 如果你们工作做好些
Perhaps if you had done your job better,
那我还能选选香草或者巧克力味
then, oh, I could choose vanilla or chocolate
或者他妈的蓝莓味 上面还有他妈的小屑屑
or fucking blueberry with fucking sprinkles on it.
但那都不是我的选择 好吗
But that's not an option for me, okay?
那个口味构不成选择  好
- That flavor's not an option for me. - Okay.
其实我觉得牙买加朗姆味也不错
You know, I think Jamaican rum is a great choice.
你的热情会对它有帮助的
And your passion about it is gonna sell it.
我混乱了 我们还是在说酸乳酪对吧
I'm confused. Are we still talking about yoghurt here?
我们就照Dan的意思做  好
- We're gonna go with Dan's idea. - Okay.
选牙买加朗姆酒口味
Jamaican rum is where we are headed.
知道吗 牙买加朗姆酒哇  好
- All right? Jamaican rum, mon. - Okay.
不错
That's good.
其实可以不要那个口音
Maybe we don't need the accent.
嘿 Dan  嗯?
- Hey, Dan. - Yeah?
Leon West现在在楼下前台等你
Leon West is down at front security for you.
Leon West? Leon West来这儿找你?
Leon West? Leon West is here for you?
那个记者? 那个专门跟咱们对着干的记者?
The journalist? The beltway butcher?
不用担心 好吗?
Don't you worry for one second, all right?
我要带他去酸乳酪店喝一杯  我一点也不担心
- I'm gonna take him to the yoghurt store. - I'm not worried.
因为你要甩了他 干掉他
Because you are gonna get rid of him. You're gonna kill him
再因谋杀终身监禁 我就再也不用见到你这张脸了
and you're gonna do life for murder and I never have to see your face again.
我要再这么勤洗手
You know, if I wash my hands anymore,
骨头都得冒出来了
the bones are gonna come through.
Dan跑哪儿去了
Hey, where is Dan?
他现在在酸乳酪店呢
He's at the yoghurt store.
Gary你还好吧 是不是病了
Gary, are you all right? Are you getting the bug?
不是 我...
No, I'm... oh!
情况有点不妙  怎么了
- Okay, you're not gonna like this. - What?
刚跟白宫发言人联系上了
White House press guys have just been in touch.
Postus想下星期从非洲回来以后
Postus wants to announce clean jobs task force
再宣布绿色产业小组的事
next week when he is back from Africa.
现在我们再次欣赏一下愤怒的副总统
We now go over live to the Vice President for her pissed-off reaction.
不是吧 他想下个星期再宣布
Come on. He wants to announce it next week.
对  好吧 这本来是我出的政策
- Yeah. - Okay, it's my policy.
他想掺和进来  天晓得 对 他的确是想掺一脚
- He's sliding in. - Who knows? Yeah, that feels like a slide.
每次都这样 不是吗  是
- This happens every time, does it not? - Yes.
就像Charlie Brown踢那个橄榄球(踢空)  对啊
- It's like Charlie Brown and the football. - Yeah.
我们又得从头做起
We're gonna have to rewind this, okay?
因为我已经让Dan去做背景调查了
Because I've got Dan backgrounding it right now.
啥 你让Dan去做那个  没错
- What? You asked Dan to do that? - Yeah, I did.
我让他去全是因为这个 副总统点二的事
I asked him because of the whole veep point two thing.
两点论
Two point me.
这个两点论 的事情
The two point me thing.
马上打给他让他别出声
Now you have to call him and tell him to stay quiet.
然后赶快去那个酸乳酪店
And you've got to go down to that yoghurt store.
你刚刚是不是对我翻白眼了
You didn't just roll your eyes, did you?
没 老大  看着就像朝我翻白眼了
- No, ma'am. - 'Cause it sure looked like it to me.
我受不了那种消极反抗的态度
I can't stand that passive-aggressive stuff.
今天都变成世界末日了
This whole day is turning apocalyptic now.
好好干 行不？
Okay?
遵命
Okay.
Leon 嗨
Leon, hi.
就在这里  行 Dan 你又不肯说干嘛要见我
- Just right in here. - Okay, Dan, a very obscure rendezvous.
所以要么你的消息够新鲜
So you either have a very hot story for me,
要么你就是来一枪崩了我的
or you're going to shoot me.
我这儿有个消息给你
I have got a story for you.
事情马上就要变得副总统口味了
Things are about to get very veep-tastic.
Egan先生 很高兴见到你
Mr. Egan. good to See you. - Anthony.
您身体还好吧
How are you, sir?
我们都很兴奋等着副总统今天大驾光临
We are very excited about the Vice President's visit today.
我们也是  我儿子用她的名字命名了一款酸乳酪
- Oh, as are we. - My son has named a yoghurt after her.
草莓味的Selina 可好喝了
Strawberry-Selina. It's very tasty.
这名真好  这位是谁
- Great name. - Who's this one?
您好 我是《华盛顿邮报》的Leon West
Leon West, ma'am. Washington Post.
我们不订这个报
Oh, we don't get the Post.
这是一个家族经营的老店
This is an old, established family store.
我们拼写的酸乳酪(yoghurt)中间是有个H的
And we spell yoghurt with an H right there in the middle.
我看到了 会记下的
I see that. I'll make a note of it.
嘿 Dan 你都不接电话呢
Oh, hey, Dan. You haven't been picking up your phone.
是啊 我有点儿忙 Mike
Yeah, I've been a little bit busy, Mike.
你好呀 Leon  嗨 Mike
- Hello, Leon. - Hi, Mike.
Mike 这位是Anthony 这家店的老板
Mike, this is Anthony, the owner of the store.
还有他可爱的母亲Maria.
And his lovely mother Maria.
你这衬衫都被汗给湿透了
You have on a very sweaty shirt.
还真是的
By golly, I do.
她直言不讳 她今年84了
She speaks her mind. She's 84.
不 女士您看着就像39岁
No. I had you pegged for 39, ma'am.
Mike可会说实话了
Mike is so good with facts.
我们俩都非常支持这届政府
We are both very big supporters of this administration.
非常感谢
We appreciate that. Thank you.
不过这可不容易啊
Although it's not always easy.
我们要交不少税啊
A lot of taxes you guys impose.
苛捐杂税  先别忙录
a ton of taxes. - Hold on a second.
苛捐杂税都要把我们生吞活剥了
Those taxes are eating us alive.
一口一口的  这个不是正式的...
- Gobble, gobble. - This isn't officially...
我们能不能先谈一下
If you'd excuse us for one moment.
Dan 能跟你单独说几句吗  一下就好
- Dan, can I talk to you for a second? - Just one second.
半路杀出个Potus 我是这么看的 就这么说
Potus Interruptus, that's what I call it. And I'm gonna tell him.
副总统女士 您不能进去参加会议
Madam Vice President, you can't go back in there for future meetings.
什么 不 老娘告诉你
What? No. Let me tell you something.
你跟那个傻逼总统说...
You tell that shit- for-brains President...
副总统女士 您能不能听我说一句
Madam Vice President, if you would listen to me for just one moment.
不 我一句也不想听
No, I won't listen to you for one second.
我一点都不想知道...  麻烦您闭嘴好吗
- I'm not interested in... - Please, be quiet!
总统现在胸很痛
The President is experiencing severe chest pains.
我们刚收到南非那边的消息
We just got word from South Africa.
您必须马上去白宫西厢
You need to get to the west wing immediately.
Oh.
真是不好意思
I'm so sorry.
女士 请这边走
Ma'am, if you could just make your way in this direction, please.
我们要去哪儿
Where are we going?
我们要带您去白宫战情室
We're gonna take you to the White House situation room.
Amy你在吗  我就在您身边
- Amy, are you here? - I am right by your side.
Gary哪去了 Gary你在吗  我在这儿
- Where is Gary? Gary, are you here? - I'm right here.
我在这儿 搞毛啊 我跟她一起的
I'm right here. What the hell? I'm with her.
我们要跑吗
Should we run?
Leon West? 在这里?
Leon West? Here?
我操 他尽跟我们对着干啊
That's the fucking beltway butcher.
你把绿色产业告诉了他没有
Have you told him about clean jobs yet?
刚要呢 屎坨坨
I was just about to, shit stack.
两位慢用  啊 多谢
- Enjoy, gentlemen. - Oh, thank you.
我们把Leon West请过来但是无料可爆
We got Leon West here and nothing to give him.
我这儿有一大堆呢  不 你没有
- I've got plenty to give him. - No, you don't.
Potus想让我们等他下个星期回来 再说绿色产业小组的事
Potus wants us to announce clean jobs task force next week when he's in town.
所以 我亲爱的朋友 你完了
So you, my friend, have your cock out at a funeral.
巧克力碎末的来啦  唔 来呀
- Sprinkles. - Oh, come on.
累死我了
Oh, God.
你新闻里写过有关酸乳酪的文章吗
Do you ever write about yoghurt in your newspaper?
没 没有 我不是写美食专栏的
No, I don't. I'm not a food writer.
那你都写些什么
What do you write?
有关政治的
I write about politics.
我对游说 辩护团体比较感兴趣
I'm interested in lobbying, advocacy groups.
你知道酸乳酪是怎么做的吗
Do you know how yoghurt is made?
不知道 不过我知道这一定很有趣
No, but I'm sure it's fascinating.
别摆出一副屈尊俯就的样子  好 给你看出来了
- Don't patronize me. - All right, you got it.
啊 先生们
Oh, gentlemen.
副总统女士  嗯
Madam Vice President. - Yes?
这些需要紧急处理
These would need to be dealt with pretty urgently
不然事态会更紧急
should the situation become more serious.
有一位来自林肯号的Reynolds上校
We have a Captain Reynolds
(华盛顿级核动力弹道潜艇)
of the U.S.S. Abraham Lincoln.
航空母舰
Aircraft carrier.
他希望大概15分钟后 进行电话会议
He's expecting a conference call in about 15 minutes
和总统 国务卿 还有Marsh将军
with the President, secretary of state and general marsh.
五角大楼的  嘘 嘘
- Pentagon. - Shh, shh.
您能名义上参与吗  可以
Could you step in notionally? - Yes.
非常感谢  毫无问题 谢谢
Thank you. - No problem At all. Thank you.
副总统女士 来杯咖啡好吗
Madam Vice President, may I get you a cup of coffee?
啊 好 谢谢你Jonah.
Oh, yes, thank you, Jonah.
不好意思 借过
Excuse me. Pardon me.
你有没有发现他...
Have you noticed how he's...
是啊 他以为我要成为他顶头上司了
Yeah, he thinks I'm about to be his boss.
嗯 顺便说一句 要是真的 第一个让他走人
Yeah, he's gonna be the first to go, by the way.
哼 好的  苟延残喘而已
- Hmm, okay. - Dead man walking.
Dan  嗯
Dan. - Yes?
能给你提个醒吗 我像个二愣子一样傻站在这儿
Can I get a heads-up? 'Cause I'm standing over here like a fucking meerkat.
其实我真有个很重要的消息给你
Yes. The truth is I had a huge story to give you.
但是现在被搁置了  哦 那我走了
- It's just been back-burnered. - Oh, sorry.
别 别 听着 Mike已经要走人了 好吗
No, no, listen. Mike is on his way out, all right?
他或者他的心腹随时会离开
Either he or his arteries are gonna quit any second.
我才是副总统办公室的新面孔 好吗
I'm the new face of the veep's office, okay?
我能给你独家新闻  你能给我独家新闻?
I Can bring you major scoops. - you Can bring me major scoops?
嘿 别介啊 绝对独家中的独家
Hey, come on, I major in major.
行了 对不起
- Stop doing that. - I'm sorry.
放这里好吗
Should I just put this right here?
行 就放下好吗  多谢
- Yeah, just put it down, okay? - Thank you.
Um...
大家伙儿能安静一下吗 非常感谢
If we could just have some quiet, please. Thank you very much.
肃静
Quiet.
女士们先生们...
Ladies and gentlemen...
我们今天相聚于此
We come here today in togetherness
满怀希望... 希望...
and in hope... certainly hope...
伟大的总统能早日康复
for the swift recovery of this great, great president
总统...
who has been a...
在保卫祖国的事情上
faultless G.P.S.
完美无瑕
in guiding our nation.
我们相聚于此 心怀勇气...
We stand here today with courage in our hearts...
额滴个神啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
让我们诚心祈祷
Let us pray.
愿圣母和圣子保佑
Holy mother of God and sweet Jesus Christ.
她在哪儿  抱歉
Where is she? - I apologize.
马上就有消息了 再等下好吗 Anthony
We'll have some information soon for you, okay, Anthony?
还有 大家随意就好
And you know what? You guys can just act naturally like you'd normally act.
好极了 正常就好  我很正常
- Great. Brilliant normalizing. - I'm normal.
好的 先生 她到底在哪儿 Dan 啊?  我不知道
- Yes, sir. Where is she, Dan, huh? - I don't know.
我蛋疼得都要爆了
My balls are comprehensively busted here.
就差去找对备用的了  听着 Mike 我问过Sue了
- I'm down to my reserve pair. - Look, Mike, I've got Sue.
她一定会打电话过来的 能别念叨了吗
She's gonna call me any second. Just give me a fucking break.
太好了 是Amy 看来我要告诉你最新进展了
Oh, bingo, Amy. I guess I'll fill you in.
Amy 到底怎么了
Amy, what the duck?
那个刺耳的坠落声
That screaming, falling sound
是我把我的耐性扔出窗的声音
is my fucking patience going out the window.
Sue?
听着Dan 这很重要
Okay, Dan, listen up. This is very important.
副总统去白宫了
The veep has gone to the White House.
总统心脏病发作了
The President is having a heart attack.
Dan 用你那傻傻的眼睛看着我
Dan, look at me with your stupid eyes.
别跟那男的讲话了 Dan 专心听我说
Stop talking to that man, Dan. Stop talking to that man and focus.
Sue 你能再说一遍吗
Sue, can you please just repeat that part on more time for me?
Selina暂时是世界上最有权势的女人
Selina is currently the most powerful woman in the world.
还有你绝对不能告诉任何人 不然你就死定了
And obviously you cannot tell anyone this or she will have you destroyed.
明白?
- Understood? - Dan...
你现在必须得给我些消息了
You have to give me something right now.
哦管他呢 反正迟早有人知道 嗯其实吧
Oh, fuck it, it's gonna break anyway. Yeah, as a matter of fact,
Selina Meyers...  一会儿就到
Selina Meyers... - is gonna come Here in a second
她要牙买加朗姆酒味配巧克力碎
and order Jamaican rum with sprinkles.
行 你的事业
Okay, your working life
八成以上毁了 听懂了没
just got 80% more fucked! Okay?
从现在开始 你这个臭小子
From now on, you bleached, plucked asshole,
你要是出了丑闻 我跟定了
I am your fucking siamese stalker.
Mike 很高兴见到你这个混蛋
Mike, always a pleasure to see you be a stupid asshole.
刚刚的那些话我可不爱听啊
I'm hearing some language that I don't like.
咋样  你说什么啊
- Yeah? - What are you saying?
算了  等一下 你们在说什么
- Forget it. - No, wait a minute. What are you saying?
他刚才说的什么啊  没事 没事
What is he talking about? - Nothing. Nothing.
你们这些家伙在自己的小世界里
No, you guys live in your own little world
一脸国会山出来的自大样
with your heads stuck up your Capitol Hill asses.
还有你 你这个基佬爱尔兰消防员... 你...你还好
And you, you gay, Irish fireman... you, you're okay.
但是你 我真不喜欢
But you, you I do not like.
Amy  什么事
Amy. - Yeah?
如果Gary病了
If Gary is sick,
我身边临时要个干事的
I'm gonna need a temporary body man.
一定的 哦 我还跟Sue说不去酸乳酪店了
Sure. Oh, and I told Sue to drop the yoghurt store.
我没这个空去想酸乳酪的事了
I don't have room in my head for yoghurt.
副总统女士 我们奉命通知您
Madam Vice President, we've been asked to tell you
您可以离开了 总统身体恢复了
that you may stand down. The President is fine.
那好极了
Well, that's terrific news.
感谢上苍  唔
- Thank God. - Mm-hmm.
看来是误报了 Potus刚刚心痛得不行
Crossed wires. Potus just suffered heartburn
就是在国宴的传统烧烤之后那会儿
after a traditional barbecue at the state function.
你绝对确信...
Are you absolutely sure that...
不是 总统他...
No, the President is...
重掌大局
back in charge of the G.P.S.
很好 很好
Super. Super.
哦 还有 抱歉 我刚刚跟Mike通了电话
Oh, and I'm sorry. I just spoke to Mike.
嗯
Yup.
他说你得马上去那个酸乳酪店
He said that you were needed down at a yoghurt store.
危机公关什么的
It was something about damage control.
是啊
Yeah.
您替总统把工作做得很好 很高兴与您共事
It's been an honor to serve such an accomplished understudy, ma'am.
你要把这个带走吗  什么
are you gonna take those with you? - What?
哦 抱歉 我是不是该还给你
Oh, I'm sorry. Should I give that to you?
谢谢  还有只笔
- Thank you. - Here's a pen.
我把它放回去 要么放这儿
I'll put it back. Do you want me to put it here?
放这儿就好  好的
- That's fine. Great. - Okay.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. - Thank you.
再见
Bye-bye.
老大 我们一个下午都在和他们情感交流呢
Ma'am, we spent a nice afternoon bonding
他们都是很好的人
with these owners. They're lovely people.
还有很多网友还在
A lot of the online guys are still here.
网友 你说真的
Online? Are you serious?
是呀 那个作用更大
Yeah. It's much more relevant.
我一直这么教育Dan
I've been telling Dan this for years.
哇 我感觉不好 挺难受的  你说笑呢
- Wow, I do not feel good. I feel bad. - You kidding?
真的 哪儿难受呢
Really? Like, where does it hurt?
不知道 很难讲
I don't know. It's hard to define exactly.
Gary不舒服是从哪儿开始的
Where did Gary's thing start?
好像是胃先不舒服
His started in, like, in his stomach.
先是胃不舒服  脸色立刻就苍白了
- It did start in his stomach? - He lost color right away, though.
你看起来...  你看起来好极了
- And you still look... - You look great.
真的  真的好极了
do I? - you Look beautiful.
多谢 好了
Thank you. Okay.
但是乳制品会对你胃不好吧
Yeah, but aren't dairy products bad for your stomach?
你现在得去喝酸乳酪
You've got to eat the yoghurt now.
我是说 好多镜头对着你呢
I mean, there will be cameras on you.
就像核战危机乳品版  没错 嗨
- This is life dairy defcon 1. - Yeah, hi.
副总统女士 这位是Anthony Holland
Madam Vice President, this is Anthony Holland,
这家店的老板  你好
The owner of The store. - How do you do?
副总统女士 欢迎光临Super Scooper
Madam Vice President welcome to Super Scooper.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
如果没问题 我们在这儿拍照片吧
I thought we'd do the photo over here, if that's okay.
好 你们这儿有
Sure. Do you have any
牙买加朗姆酒味的吗
Jamaican rum flavor?
抱歉 我没有
I'm sorry, I don't.
我还把草莓Selina这款酸乳酪也都扔了
And I've also thrown out all of the Strawberry-Selina.
哦  味道不好
Oh. - It had a bad taste.
哦 真遗憾
Oh, that's a shame to hear that.
我只剩香草味的了
All I have left is vanilla.
好  希望您喜欢
Okay. - I hope you Like that.
香草味的就好  媒体朋友们
- That'll be fine. - Members of the media.
这些是媒体朋友 大家过来吧
This is the media here. Come on in, guys.
就这些  是的
- Just this? - Yeah.
你们在这儿  看着好极了
- You guys will be right here. - Oh, that's fantastic.
嗯 其实两个小时之前口味会更好
Yeah, well, it would have been better about two hours ago.
Amy 你要...
Amy, you're gonna need to...
当然
Of course.
Amy  什么
- Amy. - Yup.
我知道 不好挪嘛
I know, it's just stuck.
照相了
We're gonna do the picture?
好了 大家伙儿 抓住这一瞬 这是真实的美国
All right, guys, get this shot. It's real America.
来一口笑一笑
Bite and smile.
是吗？ 嗯
Yeah? - Mmm.
味道不错吧  唔唔
- It's good, huh? - Mm-hmm.
再来一张
You know, let's get one re.
快点儿
Really quick.
我觉得... 要么来一张...
I think you... probably just one...
你还好吧
Are you okay?
能给你拿点什么吗
Can I get you something?
拍好了吧 大家回去吧
I think we got it, guys. Take a step back.
我得马上去趟洗手间
I have to use the bathroom right away.
能用下您的洗手间吗  不好意思 我妈妈现在在里面
- Can we use your bathroom? - No, I'm sorry, my mother is in there.
她84了 得要好一会儿才能出来呢
She's 84. She takes a while.
好吧 那么我们要走了 谢谢了  好
- Okay, then we're gonna go, but thanks. - Okay.
副总统女士 您会对税收制度做点什么吗
Madam Vice President, are youna do anything about taxes?
嗯 我要...我要减税
Yeah, moving... I'm moving them down.
哦 我找不到方向了
Oh, I don't know where this is headed.
好的 往这里走
Okay, let's go this way, then.
好啦 我们现在只要到车那边...
Nice, we'll just move to the car and get it...
手脚麻利些
Moved quickly.
Oh! Ooh-ooh! Oooh-ooh!
我不能...
I can't...
你要不要攥着我的手或者别的什么的
Do you need to squeeze my hand or something?
怎么了  要帮忙吗
- What's up? - Need help?
好吧  我必须双腿并拢
- Okay. - I can't uncross my legs.
好  哦 天呐 好吧 我来
- Yeah. - Oh, God. Okay. I get it.
各位 做个人墙环绕在副总统身边
Uh, guys, we need a wall around the Vice President.
不许拍照 一张也不行
No photos. No clean photos.
走
Here we go.
走 动起来 车来了 门开了
Here we go. Let's move. Car's open. Door open.
把她送进去 加把劲
Let's get her in. Come on.
哦 不是吧 锁上了
Oh, no. Is it locked?
开着的  上上上
- It's open. - Here we go. We're good.
把她送进去 放进去
Get Her in. - Dump Her in there.
小心 小心
Be careful. Careful.
没人会说什么  别进来
- No one's judging. - Don't come in.
别进来  副总统 我要...
- Don't come in here. - Ma'am, I'm gonna...
我...我得跟着你进去 抱歉
I-I got to go with you ma'am, I'm sorry.
低头进去  我必须
just dive into it. - I have to.
见鬼
Aw... shit.
好 快进去 快点
Okay, get your ass in. Come on.
好了 好了
All ght, all right.
嗯 我还是走回去吧 办公室见
You know what? I could use a walk. I'll meet you guys there.
我系不上安全带
I can't put on my seat belt.
没事 就这么待着
It's fine. Just stay there.
Gary把纸巾都放哪儿了
Where does Gary put those wipes?
哦 神呐
Oh, my God.
Whew.
靠
Damn.